Hello guys welcome to
youtube0 related ITC is going to
give a dividend of Rs. 100 per share to its shareholders, the
record date is 4th July,
if you have ITC shares in your account before that then
you will be eligible for the dividend. The
second news is about Jio Financial
Services Limited. Jio
Financial Services will take
share holder's approval for foreign investment through equity.
This is
a very good step by Jio Financial Services so that it can
diversify and expand its portfolio
internationally. Next news is
about ICAI Lombard. ICAI Lombard
General Insurance Company has
received GST showcase notice for 2020 of Rs. 28
crores.
So let's see about the Interaction. The
result of Interaction has just been released
where a growth of Rs. 106 crores has been seen on year to year basis.
In the results, the
consolidated net profit is Rs. 185 crores
in the fourth quarter and if it is compared
with the last year quarter, then the last
quarter was  The revenue from operations of Rs 99 crore
appeared to be increasing.
Next, let's talk about Honsa Consumer. The
results of this company have just been
delayed. This company sells
personal care and makeup products. The
company's consolidated net profit after
tax has just come in at Rs 304.8 million. Last year, the
company had a loss of Rs 1.62 billion. So
friends, till now we have seen the news.
Now let's see a little sector wise
how the sectors have performed. You must be
looking at this graph. In this graph, you can
see that Nifty Auto has performed the most today.
Nifty Auto has given a rally of 2.25 points.
If you look at Nifty, then Nifty has
rallied today at 1.64,
which is a very good rally. Also,
if you look at who has given a
big performance today, then
Nifty Health Care has given a big performance today. Okay, so let's also
see which stocks in Nifty Auto have
performed well.
You can see Nifty  You must be seeing in auto
that the share which has performed the most is
MNM which has increased from 88 today,
gain of 35, friends you have already seen the gain of 35
in MM, along with that on the second
number is R Motor which has shown a rally of 157 points
which is
3.35 which comes on the third number
maruti.com